And there
hand
i miss you i miss how you roll.
No need to fight
It's Cara.
Actually I wanted to take 1 van Guy and then I took 1 look at the prices of the
Vans and everything was very expensive I said bro why not take 1 combosa?
So then I have some really crazy plans.
That's when I'm going to show you the big deal.
That's.
I would like to hold My Little Hand How We Will Run We Will How We Will.
I was looking for a car that had room for me to assemble my things.
There's already this iron railing that I can hang my notes on.
I can put together a coffee stop so I can make some money
so I can make a bed here at the end,
then I make like those mobile beds.
You know it doubles like Jaspion's house.
Oh I know I won't be able to do everything in such a short
time but I can make this business very interesting.
Lots of idea here.
It's not connected uncle.
Let me see this part of the front here now we've got the little guy deal.
I would like to hold my hand.